[{"question": "  okay, great! bye.  so guess who&#146;s coming to thanksgiving dinner?", "answer": " sidney poitier? hehheh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": "  i miss rachel.  no, my parents.", "answer": " oh! that&#146;s great, they haven&#146;t seen the place since i moved", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": "  why can&#146;t i tell them that we live together?", "answer": " because they don&#146;t know we&#146;re dating.  do you think we should eat in the kitchen?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " why haven&#146;t you told them?!", "answer": " um, well, i was going to, i-i-i really was. but um, then somewhere, just out of nowhere, i didn&#146;t.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " why haven&#146;t you told them?! wouldn&#146;t they be happy?!", "answer": "  so! dinner in the kitchen around four! i&#146;ll see you then.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " why wouldn&#146;t they be happy?", "answer": " well, um, because mainly, um, they don&#146;t like you. i&#146;m sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " what? what? why?!", "answer": " maybe because you used to be aloof, or that you&#146;re really sarcastic, or that, y&#146;know, you joke around all the time. or that you take off your clothes and throw them on the couch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " is this why they don&#146;t like me or why you don&#146;t like me?", "answer": " look, i know that i should&#146;ve told them. i know i shouldn&#146;t care what they think. i&#146;m sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " y&#146;know, it&#146;ll be okay. it&#146;ll be okay. because when they come over, i will be all charming, i will make them fall in love with me, and then we&#146;ll tell &#145;em.", "answer": " you really think that&#146;ll work?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " hey, i can be pretty charming, babe, i won you over, didn&#146;t i?", "answer": "  i don&#146;t think you&#146;ll ever get my parents that drunk!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": "  yes, of course they like you!", "answer": " well monica just told me that they don&#146;t.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": "  yeah, they don&#146;t like you.", "answer": "  do you know why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " i dunno, maybe it&#146;s because you&#146;re really sarcastic. or maybe it&#146;s cause you uh-", "answer": "  well if people don&#146;t know they shouldn&#146;t just guess!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " this is great, another thanksgiving with nothing to give thanks for.", "answer": " maybe i could give thanks for you shuttin&#146; up, eh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " maybe i could give thanks by taking my playstation over to my new apartment.", "answer": " well maybe i love ya&#146;.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " .  janine : hey.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": "  no i don&#146;t want to play video games, joey!", "answer": " are you guys going to chandler&#146;s for thanksgiving?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " yeah! yeah, why? what&#146;s up?", "answer": " well, me and my dancer friends are thinking of doing thanksgiving uptown. i thought you guys might like to come.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " for real?", "answer": " no, but you should go to chandler&#146;s. because none of us knows how to cook, we&#146;ll probably just end up drinking all day.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " ye-ye, we go to yours!", "answer": " yeah, see, we-we-we have to stop across the hall, because it&#146;s my sister. but, uh, uh y&#146;know actually, growing up with a sister was nice because it really helped me understand women. yeah, you-you should tell your friends that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " hey! hey, pheebs, check it out. yeah, for my desert, i have chosen to make a traditional english trifle!", "answer": " wow, that sounds great! and what are you making monica, in case rachel&#146;s dessert is... so good that i eat all of it. there&#146;s none left for anybody else!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " nothing.", "answer": "  nothing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " no, sweetie, i-i trust you.", "answer": " so, if-if i mess this up, there&#146;s nothing else for dessert?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " you&#146;re not gonna mess it up.", "answer": " wow, monica, i love that, you really have faith in me. thank you. technical question, how do you know when uh, the butter&#146;s done?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " well, it&#146;s done about two minutes before it looks like that.  joey and ross: hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " oh, ooh the food smells great, mon!", "answer": " and the place looks so nice!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " yeah, hey hey, happy thanksgiving everybody!", "answer": " happy thanksgiving!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " happy thanksgiving!", "answer": " well, this has been great!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " whoa whoa whoa! where&#146;re you goin&#146;?", "answer": " oh, oh, we did say we&#146;d stop by this little thing joey&#146;s roommate is having.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " oh, janine, the really hot dancer girl?", "answer": " some would say she&#146;s attractive, yes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " and who else is going to be there?", "answer": " uh, some of her friends, yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " her dancer friends?", "answer": "  yes, all right? all of her hot dancer friends are gonna be there and they&#146;re gonna be, be drinkin&#146; and dancin, and we really wanna go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": "  dude, we were good!", "answer": " you&#146;re not gonna go anywhere, you said you were gonna eat here, and you&#146;re gonna eat here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " yeah, and-and leaving us to go see hot dancer girls is not very thanksgivingy.", "answer": " oh, but-but it is, uh, it&#146;s just like the first thanksgiving, when the indians and the pilgrims uh, sat down to dinner.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " hello everybody!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " dad , mom . look! look who it is it&#146;s chandler!", "answer": "  oh yes of course, hello chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " whoa, snowing out there?", "answer": "  no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " dad, chandler was just laughing at your joke.", "answer": " my joke wasn&#146;t funny.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " rach, rach, i just remembered. i had a dream about mr. geller last night.", "answer": " really?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " y&#146;know dad, chandler is one of ross&#146;s very best friends!", "answer": " yeah, ross sure is a great guy, y&#146;know i&#146;ve always felt that how a young man turns out is a reflection on his father.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " rach, you&#146;re killin&#146; us here, will ya serve the dessert already? those drunken dancers are waiting!", "answer": "  look at it, isn&#146;t it beautiful?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " yeah, yeah, what is it?", "answer": " it&#146;s a trifle. it&#146;s got all of these layers. first there&#146;s a layer of ladyfingers, then a layer of jam, then custard, which i made from scratch,  then raspberries, more ladyfingers, then beef sauteed with peas and onions,  then a little more custard, and then bananas, and then i just put some whipped cream on top!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " w-what was the one right before bananas?", "answer": " the beef? yeah, that was weird to me, too. but then, y&#146;know, i thought &#147;well, there&#146;s mincemeat pie,&#148; i mean that&#146;s an english dessert, these people just put very strange things in their food, y&#146;know.  oh! by the way, can i borrow some rum from your place?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " y-sure!", "answer": "  and while i&#146;m gone don&#146;t you boys sneak a taste. joey and ross:  okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " oh my god, the pages are stuck together!", "answer": "  chandler!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " oh my god, she-she made half a english trifle, and half a...sheperd&#146;s pie!", "answer": "  oh man! now she&#146;s gonna start all over! we&#146;re never gonna get to introduce the hot girls to the new world!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " no, no, we will. we just won&#146;t tell her she messed up.", "answer": " just let her serve the beef-custard thing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " yeah, it&#146;ll be like a funny thanksgiving story!", "answer": "  vomiting stories are funny...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " joey, god, your apartment is like a hundred degrees!", "answer": " did-did it make you wanna walk around in your underwear?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " no!", "answer": "  still not hot enough!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " rachel?", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " mom, uh, chandler was just saying how beautiful your sweater is.", "answer": " oh, thank you chandler! i just bought it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " what&#146;s the matter with him?", "answer": "  i think he&#146;s stoned again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": "  what?", "answer": "  what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " okay, i think i might know why my parents don&#146;t like you.", "answer": " you do? why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " okay, remember, we were young. hey, spring break, sophomore year, i got high in my bedroom and my parents walked in and smelled it and so i told them that you had gotten stoned and jumped out the window.", "answer": " what?! why did you do that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " i don&#146;t know, aheh, your&#146;s was the first name that-that popped into my head, i&#146;m i&#146;m sorry. i-i didn&#146;t think it would matter.", "answer": " how could it not matter?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " how was i supposed to know we&#146;d end up being friends after college, let alone you-you would be living with my sister?", "answer": " what about all that &#147;friends forever&#148; stuff?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " mom and dad just sent me in here to find out if you  were trying to get ross stoned!", "answer": " your parents caught ross smoking pot in college and he blamed it on", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " ross, i can&#146;t believe you&#146;d do that!", "answer": " the reason we haven&#146;t told them we&#146;re together is because they hate me, okay? so will you fix this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " okay, okay, i&#146;ll tell &#145;em it wasn&#146;t chandler who got high. now who should i say it was?", "answer": " you! it&#146;s not like it&#146;s a big deal! you-you don&#146;t still do it or anything!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " dad, please don&#146;t pick your teeth out here! alright, and if you&#146;re gonna put your feet up, why don&#146;t you sit on the-", "answer": " monica, leave him alone!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": "  will you hurry up? did you not hear me before when i told you that all of janine&#146;s friends are dancers?! and that they&#146;re going to be drinking alot!?", "answer": "  no, i did, but tell me again, because it&#146;s so romantic.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " well you&#146;re whippin&#146; so slow! can&#146;t you do it any faster?", "answer": " joey! come on! i don&#146;t wanna make any mistakes, alright? this is the only dessert and if i screw it up everybody's gonna be like &#147;oh, remember that thanksgiving when rachel screwed up the trifle?&#148;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " so why don&#146;t you just let me worry about making the trifle and you just worry about eating it, alright?", "answer": " oh i am!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " ross, if you don&#146;t tell them, then i will!", "answer": " okay, fine!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " ross! can i talk to you for a second?", "answer": " oh, uh, can it wait a second joey? i have to tell my parents something. no it can&#146;t? okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " okay, look, i think we have to tell rachel she messed up her dessert.", "answer": " what?! what is with everybody? it&#146;s thanksgiving, not...truth-day!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " look, when everyone eats that...that...banana-meat thing, they&#146;re all gonna&#146; make fun of her, do you want that?", "answer": " okay, okay, we&#146;ll just get everyone to act like they like it. that-that way noone makes fun of her and we still get to go to sweet potatoe pie!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " hey rach, can i talk to you outside for a second?", "answer": " okay...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " what&#146;s up, ross?", "answer": " so um...thanksgiving. the holiday season is upon us, hm?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " yeah!", "answer": " and um...you look nice today.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " oh no. no ross, don&#146;t do this.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " i just- i don&#146;t think us getting back together is a good idea.", "answer": "  eh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " i thought this might happen today. ross, i know the holidays can be rough. y&#146;know? and it&#146;s probably really hard for you to be alone right now.", "answer": "  you&#146;re alone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " no, i-i live with phoebe. i mean you&#146;re  alone, alone. and i just-it&#146;s just not the time for us. i&#146;m sorry.", "answer": "  ah well, can&#146;t blame a guy for trying!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " oh and  okay, and uh if anyone needs help pretending to like it, i learned something in acting class, try uh, rubbing your stomach  or uh, or saying &#147;mmm&#148; and uh, oh oh! and smiling , okay?", "answer": " yeah, i&#146;m not gonna pay for those acting classes anymore.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " rachel, there you are! come on, let&#146;s serve that dessert already!", "answer": " joey, you&#146;re gonna have to stop rushing me, you know what? you don&#146;t get any dessert.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": "  really?", "answer": " no, i&#146;m just kidding i would never do that to you! okay, everybody, it&#146;s trifle time!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " so, now, rach, this is a traditional english trifle, isn&#146;t it?", "answer": " it sure is.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " wow. so then did you make it with beef or eggplant?", "answer": " beef.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " alright, monica, i want you to have the first taste.", "answer": " really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " oh oh oh, wait! you only got whipped cream in there! ya gotta take a bite with all the layers!", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " well?", "answer": "  mmmm! it&#146;s good!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " really? how good?", "answer": " it&#146;s so good, that i feel really selfish about being the only one who&#146;s eating it, that i think we should have everyone taste how good it is. especially ross.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": "  mmm.", "answer": "  yeah, this is so good, that i&#146;m gonna go enjoy it on the balcony so that i can enjoy the view whilst i enjoy my dessert.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": "  i&#146;ve gotta call my friend mary and tell her how good this is, from monica&#146;s room.", "answer": "  i&#146;ll help you dial.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " it tastes like feet!", "answer": " i like it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " are you kidding?", "answer": " what&#146;s not to like? custard? good. jam? good. meat? gooooood.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " rachel, come here.  okay, i was just starting to take my thanksgiving nap, and i had another dream about jack.", "answer": " oh, phoebe, do i wanna hear this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " i dunno, let&#146;s see! so, okay, i dreamt that we were gonna get married, and he left, becuz he had to go fight a fire. and, um, so okay, i went to a night club, and i saw him making out with a girl.", "answer": "  oh my god, he dream-cheated on you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " boy, i&#146;m glad i wore the big belt today.", "answer": " five minutes ago, a line like that would&#146;ve floored me. now nothing. well, not nothing, i am still a woman.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " ross? let&#146;s go.", "answer": " oh yeah, about telling mom and dad, i was thinking about maybe writing a letter.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " alright, you know what? that&#146;s it. you&#146;ve had your chance.", "answer": " wha-what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": "  mom! dad! ross smoked pot in college! mr. and mrs. geller: what?!", "answer": "   you are such a tattletale! mom, dad, you remember that-that time you walked in my room and smelled marijuana? mr. and mrs. geller: yes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " well i told you it was chandler who was smoking the pot but it was me. i&#146;m sorry.", "answer": " it was you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": "  i love jacques cousteau!", "answer": "  i wasn&#146;t supposed to put beef in the trifle!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": "  i wanna gooooooo!", "answer": "  that&#146;s alot of information to get in in thirty seconds! alright joey, if wanna leave, just leave. rachel, no you weren&#146;t supposed to put beef in the trifle. it did not taste good. phoebe, i&#146;m sorry, but i think jacques cousteau is dead.  monica, why you felt you had to hide the fact that you were in an important relationship is beyond me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " and we kinda figured about the porch swing.", "answer": " ross, drugs? divorced? again?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " what happened son?", "answer": " i-i uh, i got tricked into all those things!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " thank you!", "answer": " no! thank you!  monica, and ross! i don&#146;t know what i&#146;m gonna do about the two of you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " you guys! it was bananas, cream, and beef! i-i just cannot believe that you ate that so that i wouldn&#146;t feel bad!", "answer": " well actually, i-i didn&#146;t eat mine. it&#146;s still in the bathroom.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " no it isn&#146;t, i ate that.", "answer": "  well we left ours in monica&#146;s bedroom.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}]